A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, [1961] 1970-1971
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files [1961] 1970-1971
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.741
This collection consists of 44,400 items.
Administrative Information
Access
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was forwarded to the library on 1974 July 19.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general files, 1970-1971; University committees files, 1969-1971; and, miscellaneous files, 1961-1971.
Organization
SERIES I: General Files, 1970-1971 Boxes 1-68
SERIES II: University Committees, 1969-1971 Boxes 69-72
SERIES III: Miscellaneous Files, 1961-1971 Box 73
Contents List
- Series I: General Files, 1970-1971
  - "A - Al" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - "An - Az" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Academic Deans 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Admissions - Applicants - "A - Z" 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - General 1970-1971 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - Reports 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Air Force and Air Force ROTC 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Air Force Academy 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Air Force - Air Force Academy, Board of Visitors 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Albemarle County Public Schools 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - General 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Medical 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Atlanta Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Baltimore Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Charlottesville Albemarle Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Charleston, West Virginia Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Clinch Valley Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Los Angeles Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Louisville Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Maryland Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Norfolk Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Richmond Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Roanoke Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Washington Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Day - Law 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Alumni News 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Fund - University of Virginia 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - American Association of University Professors 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education 1970-1971 (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education Newsletter - "Higher Education and 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - National Affairs"
  - American Council on Education report: A Rating of Graduate Programs 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Annual Reports 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Applications for Positions - "A - Z" 1970-1971 (Box 5)
  - Architecture - General 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Architecture - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Army - ROTC 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Army - General 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Army - Judge Advocate General's (J. A. G.) School 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Art 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Art Commission 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Asian Studies Consortium 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Association of American University Membership Committee 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Universities 1970-1971 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Universities - Committee on Membership 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Association of American Universities Study: "Review Materials for 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - membership Committee, April 1971" (Personal copy of Edgar F. Shannon, Jr.)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Astronomy 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - General 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - Football 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - ACC 1970-1971 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - Finances 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - NCAA 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Rowing Team 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - 3-2-2 Committee 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Invitations to Games 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, V. P. I., 12 September 1970 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Duke, 26 September 1970 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Wake Forest, 3 October 1970 - Homecoming 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, V. M. I., 10 October 1970 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Army, 17 October 1970 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, William and Mary, 24 October 1970 - Commonwealth Day 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, North Carolina, 31 October 1970 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, North Carolina State, 7 November 1970 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Colgate, 14 November 1970 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, University of Maryland, 21 October 1970 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Athletics - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Athletics Council of the U. S. 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Atomic Energy Commission 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Attorney General (State) 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Audit Reports 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - "B - Bm" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - "Bn - Bz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 10)
  - Biology - General 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Biology - Mountain Lake 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Biophysics 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Black Culture Week, 14-20 February 1971 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Black Culture - Black Economic Development 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Budget - Director's Office 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Budget - Capital Outlay 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Budget - Miscellaneous Information 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Budget - Requests 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Building Program (See Dept. concerned) 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds - General 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Bursar 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Business and Finance 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - Business Manager 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - "Ca -Cb" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 11)
  - "Ce - Ck" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - "Cl - Cz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 12)
  - Cavalier Daily 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Center for Advanced Studies 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Center for Study of Science, Technology, and Public Policy 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Chemistry - General 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - The Chronicle of Higher Education 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Civil Defense 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Civil Rights 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Classics 1970-1971 (Box 13)
  - Clinch Valley College - General 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Clinch Valley College - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Clinch Valley College - Building Program 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - College Entrance Examination Board 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - General 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Comptroller 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Comptroller - Department of Accounts (State) 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Computer Center 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Consultative Resource Center on School Desegregation of U.Va. 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Council of Presidents 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Council of Southern Universities (see also Southern Fellowship Fund) 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - "Da - De" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - "Df - Dz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Danforth Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Darlington School - Board of Trustees 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Data Processing 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Deans Luncheons 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Degrees 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Development Applicants 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Director of Development 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Ditchley Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - "E" - Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Economics 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Education 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Education - Annual Report, The Curry Memorial School of Education 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Education - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Educational T. V. 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Endowment Fund 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Engineering and Buildings (Hamner) 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Engineering - General 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - English 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Enrollment 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Environmental Science 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Faculty - General 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Faculty - Orientation and Reception 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Committee 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Departmental Chairman 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - General 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel, "A - Z" 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fair Labor Standards Act 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Federal Executive Institute 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - General 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Cross 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Du Pont 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Fulbright 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Hoxton 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Love 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Rhodes 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Finals - Programs 1970-1971 (Box 18)
  - Finals 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Fine Arts Center 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Ford Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Foreign Student Advisor 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Founder's Day 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - "G" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 20)
  - General Assembly 1970-1971 (Box 20)
  - General Studies - General 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Central Virginia Center 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Eastern Shore Branch - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Hampton Roads Center 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Hampton Roads Center - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg Branch 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Lynchburg - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - General Studies - Northern Virginia Center - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Branch 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - General Studies - Patrick Henry Branch - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - General Studies - Richmond Center 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - General Studies - Richmond Center - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - General Studies - Roanoke Center 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - General Studies - Roanoke Center - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - General Studies - Southwest Virginia Center 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - George Mason College - Building Program 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - George Mason College - General 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - George Mason College - Monthly Reports (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - George Mason College - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - George Mason College - James M. Shea, Jr. 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - Germanic and Slavic Languages 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - Gifts and Grants - Correspondence 1970-1971 (Box 23)
  - Gifts and Grants: January - March 1970-1971 (Box 23)
  - Gifts and Grants: April - May 1970-1971 (Box 24)
  - Gifts and Grants: June - July 1970-1971 (Box 24)
  - Gifts and Grants: July - September 1970-1971 (Box 25)
  - Gifts and Grants: October - December 1970-1971 (Box 25)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Governor's Advisory Board 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Governor's Management Study 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Governor's Office 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Graduate Business Sponsors 1970-1971 (Box 26)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - Graduate Business Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration - Report: AACSB Accreditation Application, University of Virginia 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - Grants-in-Aid for Students with Culturally-Limited Backgrounds 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - Graphics 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - Guggenheim Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 27)
  - "H - Hi" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - "Hi - Hz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Harvard Graduate Society Council 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act of 1971 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act - Title I 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act - Title II 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act - Title III 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act - Title IV 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act - Title V 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act - Title VI 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Act - Title VIII 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Higher Education Amendments of 1968 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Highway Department 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - History 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Honors Program 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Honors System and Honors Committee 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Housing 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - Huff Fund 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - Information Services 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - Institute of Government 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - Institutional Analysis 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Statistical Information University of Virginia, Nov. 1970 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: The Academic Record of Students Entering the U.Va. 1962 - 1970 Who Took Advanced Placement Examinations: A Fourth Report 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Distribution of Undergrad and Graduate Grades, First Semester, 1970-1971 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Analysis of Bachelor Degree Recipients, School of Nursing, 1970 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Distribution Credit Hours... by School and Faculty Rank, First Semester 1970 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Analysis of... Undergrad Applicants to College of Arts and Sciences, Architecture, Engineering and Applied Science 1966-1970:... Enrolled, Not Enrolled, Denied 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Full-Time Equivalent Students - Arts and Sciences by Field and Student Level, 1970-1971 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Status of Undergraduate Classes Entering in 1961-1965 U.Va. - Five Years After Entrance 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Graduate Degrees Awarded in June and August 1965-1970, by Fields and Advisors 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Students Who Entered the College of Arts and Sciences, Fall of 1970, Distributed by Fields Named as Intended Majors and by Sex 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Institutional Analysis Office Report: Distribution of Undergrad and Graduate Grades, Second Semester 1965-1970 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "A" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "B" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "C" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "D" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "E" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "F" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "G" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "H" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "I" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "J" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "K" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "L" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "M" 1970-1971 (Box 30)
  - Invitations - "N" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "O" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "P" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "Q" (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "R" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "S" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "T" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "U" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "V" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "W" 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "X" (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "Y" (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Invitations - "Z" (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 31)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Monthly Reports 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - Thomas Jefferson Center (folder empty) 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - Jefferson Society 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 32)
  - Law - Admissions 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Law - General 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Law - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Law Enforcement and Education Program 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Lectures 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Legal - General 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Legal Adviser 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Legal - Estates - Chester F. Carlson - Bequest 1970-1971 (Box 33)
  - Legal - Kirstein et al 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - Library - Board of Alderman 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - Library - General 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - Library - Microfilm Project 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - Library Associates 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - Council on Library Resources 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - McConnell Award (see T. J. Award) 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - McGregor Fund 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - McIntire Fund 1970-1971 (Box 34)
  - "Ma - Mi" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 35)
  - "Mj - Mz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 35)
  - Madison Hall (YMCA) 1970-1971 (Box 35)
  - Marine Science 1970-1971 (Box 36)
  - Mariner's Museum 1970-1971 (Box 36)
  - Markle Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 36)
  - Mary Washington College - General 1970-1971 (Box 36)
  - Mary Washington College - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Mary Washington College - Financial 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Mary Washington College - Bulletins 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Mary Washington College - Phi Beta Kappa Chapter 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Mathematics 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - General 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - Vice-President for Health Sciences 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - Medical School 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - Admissions 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - Hospital 1970-1971 (Box 37 - 39)
  - Medical Center - Nursing 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - Medical Center - Nursing Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - Medical Center - Monthly Statistical Reports 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - Medical Center - Operating Budget and Reports 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - Medical Center - Reports on Current Operations 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - Mental Health 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - James Monroe Foundation and Library 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - Mt. Lake Conference 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - Music 1970-1971 (Box 40 and 41)
  - "Na" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 42)
  - "Ne - Nz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 42)
  - NASA (see also VARC) 1970-1971 (Box 42)
  - National Association of State University and Land-Grant Colleges - General 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - NASULGC - Office for Advancement of Public Negro Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - NASULGC - Committee on Legislation 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - NASULGC - Office of Institutional Research 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - NASULGC - Circular Letters 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - NASULGC - International Programs Office 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - National Commission on Accrediting 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - National Defense Education Act (National Defense Student Loan) 1970-1971 (Box 43)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - National Historical Publications Commission 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - National Science Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - National Science Foundation - Office of Institutional Programs Advisory Commission for Institutional Relations 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - National Science Foundation - Institutional Grants for Science 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - National War College 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - Navy - General 1970-1971 (Box 44)
  - Navy - ROTC 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Navy - Minutes and Amended Constitution, Association of Naval ROTC Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Naval History Advisory Committee 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Naval History 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Navy League of the U. S. 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Newcomb Hall (see also Comm. University Union) 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - News Letter 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Oceanic Educational Foundation 1970-1971 (Box 46)
  - Office Invoices - July 1970 - October 1970 1970-1971 (Box 46)
  - Office Invoices - November 1970 - June 1971 1970-1971 (Box 46)
  - Office Travel 1970-1971 (Box 47)
  - "P - Ph" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 47)
  - "Ph - Pz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 47)
  - Personnel Correspondence - Richmond and Local Offices 1970-1971 (Box 47)
  - Personnel - Relative Applications, "A - Z" 1970-1971 (Box 48)
  - Personnel - Employee Relations 1970-1971 (Box 48)
  - Personnel - Robert C. Banks (Grievance) 1970-1971 (Box 48)
  - Personnel - Hearing Committee Appeal, John R. Burke 1970-1971 (Box 48)
  - Personnel - Hearing Committee, Appeal of Mrs. Joan Garrison 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Associates 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Council 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Philosophy 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Physics - Personnel 1970-1971 (Box 49)
  - Physics - Professor Lawrence Cranberg 1970-1971 (Box 50)
    *RESTRICTED*
  - Physics - Report of the Committee on Contractual Relations of the Assembly of Professors Concerning the Issue of Academic Freedom in the Case of Professor Lawrence Cranberg, Department of Physics 1970-1971 (Box 50)
  - Report of the Committee submitted 14 February 1969 1970-1971 (Box 50)
  - Physics - Professor Lawrence Cranberg 1970-1971 (Box 50)
  - Physics - General 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Placement 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Planning Department 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Planning Division (State) 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Project Status Reports 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Provost 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Psychology 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Public Affairs 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - Purchasing 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - Questionnaires and Inquiries 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - Radiation Protection 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - Radio 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - Raven Society 1970-1971 (Box 52)
  - Recommendations 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - Registrar - General 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - Registrar - Space Reservation Request 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - Registrar - Student Reports 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - Religious Studies 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - Reports to the University Community 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - Research Accounting and Control 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - Romance Languages 1970-1971 (Box 53)
  - ROTC 1970-1971 (Box 54)
  - "S - Sl" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 54)
  - "Sm - Sp" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 55)
  - "Sq - Sz" Miscellaneous 1970-1971 (Box 55)
  - Salaries (see also Personnel) 1970-1971 (Box 55)
  - Senate, University 1970-1971 (Box 55)
  - Seven Society 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Sociology and Anthropology 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Southern Fellowships Fund 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1970-1971 (Box 56)
  - Southern University Conference 1970-1971 (Box 56)